Anna's Metal Breath
I expected this. Looks like you're still coughing.
Could it be a cold?
A cold?
Do Metal Cardbots catch colds too?
Could it be a gremlin pulling a prank?
A gremlin?!
It's a goblin that lived on planet Machina.
If one of those things catches you, it can make your engine stall, and cause your brakes to stop working.
So that's what catching a cold means to you guys.
It's all just superstition! I've never seen any gremlins!
You wouldn't know a gremlin even if it hit you in the face!
How 'bout if I hit a gremlin in the face?!
Achoo!
It's getting cold... let's head back, guys.
You seem a little different today.
Me? I'm the same as ever.
Everyone... take back!
Uncle Edo... please take care of Fleta Z's engine.
I'll try, but planes aren't exactly my specialty.
Oh, come on, Uncle Edo! I know you can do it!
We know you're the best mechanic for the job!
We believe in you!
Haha... I'll try my best.
...Ugh.
What? A cold?
Is Jun alright?
Jun's parents called him out sick.
It's the first time he's missed school for a cold, isn't it?
He seemed fine yesterday...
Could it be...
A gremlin's prank?!
This little troublemaker ate 10 bowls of ice cream at once.
And then he slept with all the windows open and his belly exposed to the cold, and ended up like this.
My goodness...
His throat is so sore, he can't even speak.
This looks serious.
The doctor said it's just a common cold. He'll be better by tomorrow if he gets his rest and plenty of sleep.
Jun... get well soon.
Hmm.
This is the perfect opportunity.
The Metal Breath might as well already be in our hands!
But... getting in way of gremlin prank means bad luck.
Wait... don't tell me you actually believe in such superstitions?
You foolish to not believe.
So now you want to lecture me on who's foolish?
No have to. We all know you are!
Hey, hey! It doesn't matter if gremlins exist or not!
If I were to lose the treasure sitting right before my very eye, I wouldn't deserve to be called Captain Black Hook.
Black Crew, set sail!
...It's not that way, though.
Looks like Captain the fool.
Quiet.
Uh... Hey Theo.
Don't you think this might be a little dangerous?
What is?
If Jun can't talk, that means... he can't use the Metal Breath to...
Right! He can't summon the Cardbots!
We need to hurry!
Hey, wait for me, Anna!
Jun has a cold?
Help us, Fleta Z! You're the only one that can protect Jun right now!
Of course I'll help you.
Really?!
Even if you say that, your engine is still sputtering out.
Still... I cannot refuse a favor from such a charming and beautiful girl like Miss Anna.
What they're after is Jun's Metal Breath!
I have an idea.
What are you going to do?
We'll be arriving soon. Prepare yourselves!
And just who are you two scallywags?
Who are we, you ask?
The sonic speed hero, Fleta Z!
The guardian of peace, Anna!
Together we are...
Z and Anna! (FX-buffaloCrush bold xl)
Foul pirates with your eyes on our treasure!
We will send you...
Back to space!!
Wohohoho...
We're not interested in either of you!
We're here for the Metal Breath!
Get out of my way!
The Metal Breath?
You mean this?
No way!
H-How do you have the treasure of Deus Machina?!
If you thought Jun was the only one that could use the Metal Breath,
you were sorely mistaken!
Strange. Me no smell Deus Machina on that little human.
That's impossible!
Uh... yeah! Is your nose blocked or something?
What?! Do you have a cold?!
Me no catch colds!
Anna! We need to get them away from Jun's house!
I'm on it!
Let's fly, Fleta Z!
Let's go!
You're not getting away!
Shoot them down, Buster Gallon!
Already on it!
Are you okay?
Y-yeah, don't worry-
Hang on tight!
Are you alright, Anna?!
Yeah! I can handle this!-
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Fleta Z? What's going on?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
Aaah!
Where are you? Fleta Z?!
You little scoundrels!
Try as you might, but your efforts are futile.
Chest Cannon...
Fire!
Guided missiles?
Anna. Hang on!
Aaaah!
Huh? Over there, little one is falling!
He abandoned his master!
Now's our chance, Black Hook!
I told you to call me captain!
Oh no...
I don't think I can keep flying. Let's take this fight back to land.
Waaah!
It sounds like they are in battle.
It must be Black Hook's gang!
So... he's fighting the three of them by himself?
What should we do? We can't help in our current state!
Woah!
Jun. Are you awake?
Ugh...
You did great out there.
Fleta Z... You were great too...
Are-are you sure you're alright?
Over there!
To think I'd get hit by my own Chest Cannon...
I've got to hand it to you for making it this far!
You not getting away this time!
Now. Hand over the Metal Breath immediately.
Oh my. This isn't good.
No waste time! Hand it over!!
Aah! Fleta Z, get down!
Watch it!
Sorry.
Buster Blaster!
Do a barrel roll!
Oh no...
Z and Anna Punch! (FX-buffaloCrush bold xl)
Z and Anna... Punch!!
Jun! I came home early today! Are you feeling any better?
Huh? Jun?
Yes! We did it!
What a disgrace...
I don't get it... why doesn't he use his bow?
How do you like the power of Z and Anna-
Oh...!
Uhh...
Metal Breath?
WHAT?!
It's fake!
That little pipsqueak tricked us!
You will not be forgiven!
Oh no! Anna! Watch out!
Captain's Cannon! Fire!
Anna... are you alright?
I... can't anymore...
Playing the Black Hook Crew for a bunch of fools? I'll make you pay for that, and with interest!
Brace yourselves!
Spinning Cutter!
What?
Haha! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Jun!
It's the small fry!
So is that the real Metal Breath this time?!
But he can't even talk with a sore throat! How were they summoned?
Jun and I are connected in spirit. We don't need words to communicate.
Don't be ridiculous.
Whatever the case may be,
you delivered yourselves right to us, so I hope you came prepared!
Now bring me the Metal Breath!
I'm getting really tired of this!
P-Phoenix Fire... setup...
B...Burning... Hammer...
Burning... Hammer!!
Buffalo Moonsault!
Forceps Shock...
Forceps Shock!
How is this... possible?!
Is this just another one of your tricks?
Fleta Z!
I'm okay now. Please try to hear Jun's voice too!
Jun's voice...?
Ah! Right!
Jun! I'm ready too!
Fleta Z!
The two of us will end the battle with Vulture Wings!
Understood!
End of the line for you!
Black Hook!
Vulture Wings!
Vulture... Wings!
Captain's Cannon!!
You are going to pay for this!
The Black Crew will never give up!
Well you should learn when to give up!
Jun! Are you alright?!
Oh, Jun...
T-Thanks, Anna... Fleta Z...
It's my duty to protect you, Jun.
I'm the one who should be saying thank you! You saved us!
You're burning up! Let's get you home!
I... can't go on!
Hang in there! Jun!!